toptalent.in 2014-07-01

# TopTalent.in - Exclusive Jobs for Students and Alumni of Top Engineering and MBA Colleges of India.

Privacy

Thank you for visiting TopTalent.in job search and hiring management Internet web site located at the URL www.toptalent.in. This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout TopTalent.in governing the use of personally identifiable information provided to TopTalent.in via this Site or otherwise. By accepting the policy at the time of registration, you expressly approve and consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy.

Due to the rapidly evolving nature of Internet, TopTalent.in may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If so, TopTalent.in will post its updated Privacy Policy on its web site. TopTalent.in encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

_Personal Information_

In order to operate the Site in an efficient and effective manner and provide users with information on job postings and services that may be of interest to them, Toptalent may collect personal information, including contact information (such as an email address), from its users. In addition, this information allows us to provide users with private and secure areas to post and modify their original content on our site (e.g., jobs and resumes). We also automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on the Site and use this information to do internal research on our users demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve users in general. This information may include the URL that a user has just come from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), the URL a user goes to next (whether this URL is on our Site or not), a user`s computer browser information, and their IP address.

You agree that TopTalent.in may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests (such as relevant job postings and services), or provides administrative notices or communications applicable to your use of the Site. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of any further receipt by following the opt-out provisions provided in each such communication.

We do not sell our user`s personal information to anyone for any reason. All users should be aware, however, that when they voluntarily display or distribute personal information (such as their email address or resume), that information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties for which TopTalent.in is not responsible. Also, you may have arrived at this Site by following a link from a TopTalent.in affiliate and the affiliate may use the information consistent with its privacy policy instead of this one. 

TopTalent.in may also disclose specific user information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of Toptalent or other users of the Site. In addition, personal information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy of TopTalent.in.

_Credit Card Security_

TopTalent.in employs encryption for secure credit card transactions. 

_About Cookies_

At TopTalent.in, we use cookies only for the protection and convenience of our users. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. If a user`s system is idle for more than an hour, however, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user`s information while they are away from their computer. You may have the ability to reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent; however, some Toptalent features or services may not function properly without cookies.

Third-Party Cookies: We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please send us an email to the email ID mentioned at the end of this page. 

_What You Should Know_

TopTalent cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site. 

_Feedback & Complaints_

It is our constant endeavor to provide unique experience in Online Recruitments. However, in the unlikely event of our services not meeting your expectations, we would like to hear from you. For speedy resolution of your complaints, it is important that your write to the correct email address as explained below.

customerservice@toptalent.in

_Help Us Monitor Fraud_

Please be advised that TopTalent will never initiate a request for your personal information via email or pop-up window. If you ever receive a request for this type of sensitive information, please do not respond and immediately contact TopTalent customer service to report the suspected fraud.

If you think you have been a victim of fraud, contact us immediately at customerservice@toptalent.in so steps can be taken for your safety.
